http://www.ssw.umich.edu/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
COVID-19 Information
Latest SSW information and resources.
Main menu
Menu
Menu
AboutMichigan Social Work AdvantageDean's WelcomeMission & GoalsContact & Building HoursDiscover Social WorkRankings, Facts & Figures
Strategic PlanOverviewMission StatementOutcomesPrintable Strategic PlanDetailed Strategic Plan
Community EngagementOverviewDetroitGlobalTraining/ResourcesPartnershipsPeopleEvents
News & EventsNewsEventsFaculty BooksOngoing MagazinePresentationsResearch PublicationsSSW PublicationsStories
COVID-19Latest UpdatesPrinciples & ResponsibilitiesBuilding Hours & EntryStudentsFacultyStaffVisitorsTestingFAQ
Diversity, Equity & InclusionOverviewDEI Welcome LetterPeopleStrategic PlanEventsToolkitSocial Work & Social Justice DialoguesDEI Impact AwardsLGBTQIA+Student Diversity
HistoryOverviewHistory of Social WorkPast Deans
Faculty OpeningsOverviewCurrent Openings
Artwork at the SSWOverviewSocial Justice Collection
Computing ResourcesOverviewPrinting Computing SitesU-M Computing Sites
AdmissionsConnect with SSWOverviewCurrent Student Virtual MeetingsProspective Student WebinarContact MSW Admissions CounselorSpeak with a
Current MSW StudentRequest MSW Program InformationMSW Brochure and Flyers
MSW ProgramOverviewApplyCourse CatalogFinancial AidLicensureOnline MSWPart-Time ProgramsPathwaysProgram LengthSpecial ProgramsStudent GuideTuition & FeesAdmitted Students
Online MSW & Certificate ProgramsOverviewOnline MSWMasterTrack
Joint PhD ProgramOverviewFundingApplyProgram StatisticsFAQJoint PhD ResearchJoint PhD Students & AlumniPhD NewsConversations Across Social Disciplines
Undergraduate MinorOverviewDeclarations and RequirementsCoursesFaculty & StaffPodCASCPoverty Solutions Certificate ProgramPreferred AdmissionsStoriesStudent BoardsFunding OpportunitiesGlobal Independent StudyAlumni
Undergraduate Social Work OptionsOverviewCommunity Action and Social Change MinorUM DearbornU-M Sociology and Social Work
International StudentsOverviewAffidavit of Financial SupportEnglish ProficiencyFinancial AidHealth InsuranceResourcesStudent StoriesTuition & FeesFAQ
ProgramsMSW ProgramOverviewApplyCourse CatalogFinancial AidLicensureOnline MSWPart-Time ProgramsPathwaysProgram LengthSpecial ProgramsStudent GuideTuition & FeesAdmitted Students
Online MSW & Certificate ProgramsOverviewOnline MSWMasterTrack
Joint PhD ProgramOverviewFundingApplyProgram StatisticsFAQJoint PhD ResearchJoint PhD Students & AlumniPhD NewsConversations Across Social Disciplines
Undergraduate MinorOverviewDeclarations and RequirementsCoursesFaculty & StaffPodCASCPoverty Solutions Certificate ProgramPreferred AdmissionsStoriesStudent BoardsFunding OpportunitiesGlobal Independent StudyAlumni
Undergraduate Social Work OptionsOverviewCommunity Action and Social Change MinorUM DearbornU-M Sociology and Social Work
Field EducationOverviewLGBTQIA StudentsProspective Field Instructors
Continuing EducationOverviewPoliciesLicensure RequirementsCertificate ProgramsCourse CatalogExam PreparationFAQMicroMasters ProgramMailing List
Global ActivitiesOverviewGlobal Activities Scholars ProgramGlobal Independent StudyPeace CorpsGlobal Social Work Practice PathwayExchange VisitorsFundingGlobal Career GuidePeople
Jewish Communal LeadershipOverviewScholarshipCourse PlanningCourses & Field PlacementsEventsStories & VideosPeople
Community Action & Research CertificateOverviewRackham Policies
ResearchResearch DiscoveriesOverviewGroups/Labs/CentersPast Discoveries
Research OfficeOverviewResponsible ConductFaculty SupportFunding OpportunitiesGrantsNewslettersProposal Notification
Program EvaluationOverviewProjectsSchedule a ConsultPeopleEvents
Curtis CenterOverviewAbout Vivian A. & James L. CurtisPartnersPeopleSignature ProgramsVideos
Family & Community WellbeingOverviewPeopleProjectsSmall Grants
LibraryOverview
PublicationsOverviewAHEAD Magazine
PresentationsOverview
Student LifeStudent LifeOverviewAnn Arbor & BeyondFootball TicketsHealth & SafetyHousingReflection RoomFAQStudents with ChildrenStudents with Disabilities
Student OrgsDirectoryResources
Career ServicesOverviewJob Search ResourcesJob PreparationLicensing & Exam PrepAlumni Employment DataGraduate AssistantshipsPost-MSW FellowshipsStudent EmploymentWriting Assistance
Getting AroundOverviewMaps & ParkingSSW Ride SharingAfter Hours Transit ServicesSSW Building Maps
InsuranceOverviewAffordable Care ActDomestic Health InsuranceInternational Health InsuranceLiability & Auto Insurance
Student Services & Enrollment ManagementOverviewFAQGraduate AssistantshipsMental Health ResourcesStudent Employment
CommencementsOverviewCeremoniesCommencement CalendarInternational Students
International StudentsStudent StoriesInternational ApplicantsFinancial AidHealth InsuranceHousingResourcesStudent ActivitiesTuition & FeesFAQ
DirectoriesCourse CatalogFall 2020Winter 2021Outside ClassesClass DescriptionsPast Terms
OfficesDirectoryDiversity, Equity & InclusionInformation TechnologyContacts by Office
OfficesFacultyTenure-Track FacultyClinical & Research FacultyResearch FellowsField EducatorsLEO LecturersEmeritus Faculty
ContactsAffiliateFacultyJoint PhD StudentsLEO & GSIResearch FellowStaffEmeritusGSSATemporaryOffices
FAQAcademics & CurriculumContinuing EducationFinancial AidInternational StudentsMSW Applications & AdmissionJoint PhD ProgramRegistrar's Office
AlumniGive
You are hereHome   /   Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your Privacy
The University of Michigan School of Social Work is committed to protecting your personal privacy. We treat your privacy as we do our own.
When you provide us with personal data, we may use that information in the following ways: provide you with School of Social Work news and events, this may include such things as upcoming reunions, newsletters, fund-raising events, donor recognition, and progress on recent fund-raising campaigns; and contact you for purposes connected to or our relationship with you.
If we use your personal data to contact you, we will provide you with a method allowing you to opt-out of future communication. You can also contact us by e-mail, writing or telephoning.
Email: ssw.msw.info@umich.edu
Phone: (734) 764-3309
View full SSW contact information.
We will not sell, share, or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information to third parties, except as required by law.
Cookies
When you view our website, we may store some information on your computer in the form of a cookie. Cookies allow us to tailor our website to better match your interests and preferences. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any of your personally identifiable information while on our site. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience all features and content of our website.
Contact Us
Press escape to close
Phone
1 (734) 764-3309
Fax
1 (734) 936-1961
Email
MSW
Get directions »
Faculty, Staff & PhDDirectory »
Building Hours & Maps
